# ĐẶNG BẢO TRUNG

Advicing Pharmacist | Male | 09/01/1995



Experience 1 year

Latest company Boehringer Ingelheim International

**GmnH Vietnam Representative** 

Office as Advicing Pharmacist

Highest education Bachelors

Languages English - Advanced

Email Baotrungblf@gmail.com

Phone +84 962661482

Address 3/45/12A Thanh Thai street, ward

14, district 10, HCMC, District 10,

Ho Chi Minh City

## **SUMMARY**

I hold a Bachelor degree in Pharmaceutical from University of Medicine and Pharmacy HCMC. Gaining more than 1 years in both Sales and Marketing in Multinational Pharmacy and Medical device coporation, with solid knowledge in Manufacturing/Pharmaceutical industries.

Short-term: Product Executive/Specialist – 5 years

Long-term: Product manager in next 10-15 years

Career Objective: Develop new skills, marketing strategy and thinking methods to deep understand customer then apply for

creation and marketing activities



## SKILL

- Communication
- Time Management
- Microsoft Office Applications
- Data Mining
- Solution Orientated
- Fast Learning and Hardworking
- Proactive Thinking

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

11/2018 - Present

## **Advicing Pharmacist**

Boehringer Ingelheim International GmnH Vietnam Representative Office

Driving Performance - Has the responsibility to meet/exceed promotion targets for assigned product(s) within the allocated territory through achievement of related promotion Excellence KPIs

- Executing Customer Engagement Excellence focuses on executing hospital, in-clinic promotion Action Plan by way of Customer Engagement Model, implements off-clinic promotional activities assigned to target Customers and thereby improves the Customer relationship
- Coordinate in the implementation of company marketing plans
- Ensures to give on time feedback to the marketing team on all marketing campaigns implemented.
- Prepare documents, company profile for tendering, honorarium, other proposal, follow up the results and notify to ASM/ RSfor further



#### support if any

- Gives customer feedback, and information on competitor activity to the marketing team so that they can respond to changing market conditions and customer demands.
- Adherence to Policies and Guidelines related to Compliance and Internal Code of Conduct - Is responsible to ensure that all company and industry compliance topics/requirements are understood adhered and established local processes followed
- Regular reports (business plan review, Marketing proposal, paperwork, honorarium, all marketing activities assigns)
- Other tasks as required by the manager.

#### 07/2018 - 11/2018

## **Marketing Assistant**

- B. Braun Vietnam Ltd
- Participate in training process for Medical Representative as supportive Trainer to build strong medical knowledge and aim to higher sales targets
- Coordinate with Product manager (PM) in creating new Marketing tools & gimmick, training resource for Closure Technologies Division.
- Prepare Contract, Compliance Review Form, Sales and Markeing request to marking events/sponsor compliance code of conduct of BBraun
- Assist PM in execution of Marketing campaigns and Internal Marketing events (Congress, Symposium, CME training with speaker tours. Etc)
- Coordinate with Medical representative, PM to liase with KOLs/HCP for listing, sales enquiries, orders/contracts



- Constant collect proposal from sales team and feedbacks from customers for adaptation/upgrading
- Assist PM in communication to external and internal stakeholders (C&B, finance, FF) for Marketing purpose news or updates
- Propose new ideas to upgrade Marketing activities
- Daily task, Paper-work, manage sample warehouse
- Any other task or duties assigned by manager

### **EDUCATION**

09/2013 - 08/2018

Bachelors Degree, Pharmacy

Bachelors - University of Medicine and Pharmacy at Ho Chi Minh city

GPA: 7,27/10

# REFERENCE

Vũ Ngọc Thùy Linh

HR Executive at Mobile World Investment Corporation (MWG) linh.vungocthuy@thegioididong.com |

